nerium.com 2015-04-21

# United States Privacy Policy

                                    United States Privacy Policy
                        UNITED STATES
The protection of personal information is very important to Nerium International™. Privacy protection is, and
always will be, critical to our business. Nerium International is committed to protecting the privacy and security
of individuals who visit Nerium International’s website(s). The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you
about what information may be collected from you when visiting the site. It explains how such information will
be used by Nerium International and/or other persons or entities with whom such information may be shared.
It also explains your choices regarding the collection, use, and distribution of such information; your ability
to edit, update, correct, or delete such information; and the security procedures that we have implemented
to protect your privacy.
Collection of Information
When visiting a Nerium International website, you may be asked for certain types of personally identifiable
information, such as your first and last name, mailing address, city, state, ZIP code, telephone number, email
address, and credit-card number in connection with automatic deposit/debits, etc. This information allows us
to conduct our business, provide customer service, communicate offers on products that may be of interest
to you, and to fulfill your order. You may volunteer to disclose personally identifiable information to us. If you
do not want to disclose your personally identifiable information to us, please do not submit it. We may also
collect non-personally identifiable information from you when you visit the site, such as your IP address,
browser type, domain name, etc. This information is collected and analyzed in the aggregate in order to
improve the function and content of our website.
Use of Information
Nerium International uses the information that is collected about you for a variety of purposes, such as
processing, confirming, and fulfilling your order; providing your name to Nerium International Brand Partners
in connection with your potential interest in our products or opportunity; analyzing Brand Partner trends
and statistics; and enhancing the operation of the site. We may employ vendors to perform functions on our
behalf. Examples may include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, email administrative functions, processing
credit-card payments, and providing customer service. Nerium International vendors are under contractual
obligation to use confidential data only for those purposes for which they are hired. We may disclose the
information that we collect about you when we have reason to believe that it is necessary to identify, contact,
or bring legal action against persons or entities that may be causing injury to you, to us, or to others. We may
also disclose information when we believe the law requires it.
Protection of Children
The Nerium International website is not designed for or targeted at children. We do not knowingly collect,
use, or disseminate any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 18. If, however,
we become aware that personally identifiable information regarding a child under the age of 18 has been
collected at the Nerium International site, we will use such information for the sole purpose of contacting
a parent or guardian of the child to obtain verifiable parental consent. If we cannot obtain consent after a
reasonable period of time, or if, when contacted, a parent or guardian requests that we do not use or maintain
such information, we will make reasonable efforts to delete it from our records. Upon request by a parent
or guardian, Nerium International will provide a description of the specific types of personal information
collected from a child who is under the age of 18.
Cookies
Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored on computer hard drives. We may use cookies to
recognize you when you return to the Nerium International site in order to provide you with a better user
experience. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information, such as your name, or sensitive
information such as your credit-card number. Web browsers often allow you to erase existing cookies from
your hard drive, block the use of cookies, and/or be notified when cookies are encountered. If you elect to

block cookies, please note that you may not be able to take full advantage of the features and functions of
the Nerium International website.
Third-Party Links
The Nerium International website may contain links to websites operated and maintained by third parties over
which we have absolutely no control. Any information you provide to third-party websites will be governed
under the terms of each website’s privacy policy, and we encourage you to investigate and ask questions
before disclosing any information to the operators of third-party websites. We have no responsibility or liability
whatsoever for the content, actions, or policies of third-party websites. The inclusion of third-party websites
on our site in no way constitutes an endorsement of such websites’ content, actions, or policies.
Security
As technology continues to enhance and expand the collection of information of all kinds, we are committed
to using our technological resources in an effort to ensure that our Brand Partners, Customers, and Users
receive the kind of privacy protection that will make them confident and secure. We shall not be responsible,
however, for harm that you or any person may suffer as a result of a breach of confidentiality due to your use
of the Internet.
Modifications to Policy
This Privacy Policy is effective as of May 2014. Nerium International reserves the right to change this Privacy
Policy at any time. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective immediately upon notice, which may be
provided to you via email or by posting the latest version on our website. Your use of the site after such Notice
will be deemed acceptance of such changes. Be sure to review this Privacy Policy periodically to ensure
familiarity with its most current version. You can easily confirm whether any revisions have been posted since
your last visit by checking the date on which the Policy was last revised, which is set forth at the bottom of
this Policy. If you disagree with the changes in our policy, please do not use the site after the posting of such
changes online. By using the Nerium International website following the posting of changes to this Privacy
Policy, you agree to and approve of all such changes.
Questions or Comments
If you have questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact the Nerium Support Center by
email at support@nerium.com or call (855) 463-7486 during normal business hours.
                                                         © 2 0 1 4 N e r i u m I n t e r n a t i o n a l ™, L L C . A l l R i g h t s R e s e r v e d . R e v i s e d 5 / 1 4 .
